[{"answer": "It's Saturday", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Find out what", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " my friend, all right..", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I told you, I just got change", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Jesus Christ. Not even close", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "NO SHE DIDN'T GET YOUR DOUBLE BURGER!! IT'S ALL FUCKIN' FLYIN' FISH FILET!", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, and we got four of 'em", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Cause fuckin' Morgan's got a crush on her, we always go there and when we get to the window he never says a fuckin' word to her, he never even gets out of the car, and she never gets our order right cause she's the goddamn MISSING LINK", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, can I help you", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No students work for me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Could you just check, because the young man who works in my buildin", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Building two", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " I am afforded the right to speak in my own defense by our constitution, Sir.  The same document which guarantees my right to liberty.", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend proclaimed", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "That you meet with me twice a week  and you meet with a therapist", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "That's right", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Like what, my friend", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What places", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That would be a monumental waste of time, wouldn't it, my friend", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I happen to know so", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Look into my eyes. I don't need therapy", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Okay... don't forget to get another therapist for next week", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What do you want to do", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Who is he", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "There is somebody..", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He was my roommate in college", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't know, it was just kind of the boring suburban thing. Private school, that place, and now Med. School.  I actually figured out that at the end of it, my brain will be worth a quarter of a million dollars. I shouldn't have told you that..", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I was happy to pay. I inherited the money", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I bet your parents were happy to pay", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Is Harvard gettin' all that money", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "that place. I'm leaving in June after I graduate", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, I'm gonna experiment on you for my anatomy class, then go", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes you have. You were thinking you were gonna get a good night kiss", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Yes you were", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, you will", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Then why don't we just get it out of the way", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Why me", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "My kind of background", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "My kind of background", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "He's from that place? How many people did you try before you came to me", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Would you excuse us", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You too, my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What did you think", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I did", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I did", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yeah, it did take me a long time", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You know, nothing special", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Do I have a lot of brothers and sisters", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "It was great. There was always someone to play with, give you advice", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "'Course I do, they're my brothers", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yeah? You got a lady now", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "How'd it go", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "So Christ, call her up", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "And right now you're perfect too. Maybe you don't want to ruin that", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Lon? He got married. He has a kid. I kind of lost touch with him after my friend got sick", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "What? Do I wonder if I'd be better off if I never met my wife", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "October 21, 1975. Game six of the World Series. Biggest game in that place history, Me and my friends slept out on the sidewalk all night to get tickets. We were sitting in a bar waiting for the game to start and in walks this girl.  What a game that was. Tie game in the bottom of the tenth inning, in steps my friend, hit a long fly ball down the left field line. Thirt", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I was havin' a drink with my future wife", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "And what kind of friends are these? They let you get away with that", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "\"I gotta go see about a gir", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "Why do we always stay here", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I've never seen your place", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "That's great, my friend, that there's interest", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "What don't I understand", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I guess so", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Like me", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Will and I dropped you off here, remember", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "This is your house, right", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "All I can say i", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Yeah, it is", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "I couldn't go 'cause I had a date. So I sent my chief negotiator", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Then don't set up any more meetings", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "I want you to come with me", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "I know. I just do", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "How do you know that", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "Yeah, but how do you know", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "I know. I just do", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I don't know. I just feel it", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "I don't know. I just feel it", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "Yeah, I'm sure", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "One, because I have a job here and two because I live her", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "I'm not sayin' I'm not in love with you", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "I'm not sayin' I'm not in love with you", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "What do you mean", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "What do you mean", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "What am I scared of", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "Yes, Will. I didn't even know that", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "Yes, I do, Will", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Yes I do. Did you ever think that maybe I could help you? That maybe that's the point, that we're a team", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "I don't want to", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": " What's up guys", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "I don't have a VCR at my house", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "I guess", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "What did I think", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "It's a way outta here", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "Look, you're my best friend, so don't take this the wrong way, but in 20 years, if you're livin' next door to me, comin' over watchin' the fuckin' Patriots' games and still workin' construction, I'll fuckin' kill you. And that's not a threat, that's a fact. I'll fuckin' kill you", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "Do you know when you'll be back", "docId": "Good-Will-Hunting.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "I got one of those too", "qsentId": 98}]